I'm Peppa Pig. [grunts]
-This is my little brother George.
-[grunts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-And this is Daddy Pig.
-[grunts]
[laughing]
Peppa Pig. [grunts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa, George, and Suzy Sheep
have had a sleepover
at Rebecca Rabbit's house.
It's fun having carrots for breakfast,
Mommy Rabbit.
Yes, we always have carrots for breakfast.
I could eat carrots all day,
but I'd better go to work.
Have a nice day.
[in unison] Bye-bye.
Mommy Rabbit, why don't you work?
I do work, Suzy. Who do you think
looks after these two little bunnies?
You do, Mommy. [giggles]
And you can help me
by tidying up your toys, please,
before someone trips over them.
[doorbell rings]
That'll be my sister.
Hello.
-Hello, Miss Rabbit.
-Aunty.
I can't stop long,
I've got lots of work to do today.
I've got the supermarket checkout,
the ice cream stall, and the bus to drive.
See you later then, sister.
Bye, sister.
Whoops. Whoa!
Miss Rabbit has tripped over one
of Richard's toys.
Oh, my ankle.
-I can still hop to work. Aah. Ooh.
-No, you stay here and get better.
But I've got so much work to do.
I'll do your work for you.
Which job is first?
The supermarket.
Okay.
Rebecca, look after your aunty.
Yes, Mommy.
Mommy Rabbit has arrived
at the supermarket.
Thank goodness you're here, Miss Rabbit.
Miss Rabbit is ill.
I'll be doing her job today.
Are you not Miss Rabbit?
No, I'm her sister, Mommy Rabbit.
Is this where I sit?
Uh, yes. Have you ever worked
a checkout before?
-No.
-How much is this?
Oh, I don't know.
-I've got a voucher.
-Do you take book tokens?
Can I pay with a card?
Um...
Suzy Sheep is dressed up
in her nurse's costume.
Don't worry. I'm only a pretend nurse.
Stick your tongue out and say, "aah."
Aah!
[telephone rings]
Rebecca Rabbit's house.
Who's speaking, please?
-It's Mommy Rabbit. Is everything okay?
-[Peppa] Yes.
Good, because this job
is gonna take me all day.
What about Miss Rabbit's other jobs?
We'll need more help.
[telephone rings]
Uh...
Miss Rabbit's ice cream stall.
Daddy. Why are you buying an ice cream?
Oh, Peppa. I was on the way to the gym
when I thought an ice cream would be nice.
[grunts] Miss Rabbit is ill.
You've got to sell the ice cream today.
Oh ho! I'm an expert at ice cream.
Can I have a cherry ice cream?
Uh... Strawberry. Vanilla.
Chocolate. Banana.
With pistachio and strawberry, please.
Ah. Strawberry.
Oh. It's melted.
How about ice cream soup instead?
[line rings]
[woofs] Granddad Dog's breakdown service.
[grunts] Miss Rabbit is ill.
Can you drive her bus today?
Of course, Peppa.
[horn honks]
[woofs] All aboard.
Mommy Sheep's car has broken down.
[phone rings]
[woofs] Granddad Dog's breakdown service.
-[bleats] Can you rescue me, please?
-I'll be straight there.
[chattering]
We would like to apologize
for any inconvenience
this may cause to your journey.
Driving a bus is quite hard.
Selling ice cream is quite hard.
Running a supermarket checkout
is quite hard.
[laughing and noisemaking]
Uh...
I'm feeling better. Can I get up now?
No, you must lie very still,
but, please, keep breathing.
[door closes]
-[Daddy Pig grunts]
-[Granddad Dog woofs]
-Are you feeling any better, Miss Rabbit?
-It's not easy doing all your jobs.
It's not easy looking after
your little bunnies.
[both laugh]
You will be back to work tomorrow,
won't you?
Yes, and you'll be back at home,
Yes.
[laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa has come
to play with Suzy Sheep.
-[giggles] Hello, Suzy.
-Hello, Peppa.
Why have you got that mask on your face?
So people don't know it's me.
I'm in a... [whispers] secret club.
Ooh. Can I be in your secret club?
Shh.
It's not easy to get in to.
You have to say the secret word.
What word?
-Flob-a-dobble.
-Flob-a-dobble?
Right, you're in.
[both giggle]
[bicycle bell rings]
Danny Dog has come to play.
[barks] Hello, Peppa. Hello, Suzy.
Shh.
-What?
-I'm in a secret club.
I'm in it, too.
-Ooh.
-[bicycle bells ring]
Pedro Pony, Candy Cat,
and Rebecca Rabbit have come to play.
-Hello.
-Shh!
[barks] Suzy and Peppa
are in a secret club.
Can we join your secret club?
It's very hard to get into.
You have to say the secret word:
Shallamakooky!
[all] Shallamakooky?
That's not the word I said.
It changes all the time to keep it secret.
-Oh.
-Are we in the secret club now?
You're in.
What do we do?
We do secret things in secret.
And secretly go on secret missions.
[giggle]
[sighs] I don't know
what you're talking about.
Show us how you do a secret mission.
[in unison] Yes. Show us.
Uh, Peppa can do it.
You've got the mask on, Suzy.
Okay.
My secret mission is to get biscuits.
Watch this.
Suzy Sheep is trying not to be seen.
Mommy, can I have some biscuits
for my friends, please?
Of course. Here you are.
Thank you, Mommy.
Suzy Sheep has returned with the biscuits.
[in unison] Hooray!
Shh!
[quietly] Hooray.
-Did anyone see you?
-No.
Well, only a grownup.
Look out.
Would you like juice
to go with your biscuits?
What biscuits?
The biscuits I just gave you
for your friends.
Oh, Suzy.
What's the matter?
We're in a secret club,
doing secret things,
and Suzy's told everyone.
Oh, can I be in your secret club, please?
Please? I've always wanted
to be in a secret club.
It's very hard to get into.
You must say the secret word.
Which is?
Pica-needle-noodle.
Pica-needle-noodle?
That's it. You're in.
What happens now?
-Look out.
-[car horn honks]
It's Daddy Pig.
You talk to my daddy.
But don't say anything
about our secret club.
Hello?
Ah. There you are, Mommy Sheep.
What's new?
[stammers]
Secret club.
Oh, no.
Ooh. I always wanted to be
in a secret club. Can I join, please?
You can't join, Daddy,
because you are grown up.
Uh, my mommy is grown up.
Well, you have to know the magic word.
Which is?
Papa-deedle-doodle-dum.
[in unison] You're in.
What do I do now?
Look out.
It's Mommy Pig.
Follow Mommy in secret.
[rustling]
Daddy Pig?
Ah. Hello, Mommy Pig.
What are you doing in that bush?
Um, uh... Secret club.
[all sigh]
I've always wanted
to be in a secret club.
We can't have everyone in the secret club.
-It wouldn't be a secret.
-Oh.
I suppose it doesn't have
to be a "secret" secret club.
[grunts] It can be
The Everybody Secret Club.
And everybody can be in it.
Oh, goody.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa, George, and Granny Pig
are going out for a day
on Grandpa Pig's boat.
[grunts] Ahoy there, Peppa and George.
-We're ready to go sailing.
-I'll move the boat a bit nearer.
Careful you don't hit that big stick,
Grandpa.
That's a mooring post. I won't hit it.
Oh.
Grandpa, there's a big hole in your boat.
It's just a scratch.
Ooh. Grandpa's boat is sinking.
Quick, Grandpa Pig, jump off.
A captain never leaves his sinking ship.
Grandpa Pig's boat has sunk
to the bottom of the river.
It is Granddad Dog.
[woofs]
Ahoy there, Grandpa Pig.
Lovely day for a sail.
Um, yes. Ahoy there.
I'm taking my boat to the boatyard today.
Going to get a few repairs done.
Eh, would you mind taking my boat
to the boatyard, too, please?
Of course.
Where is your boat?
Um, I'm standing on it.
[laughs] Has it sunk?
Well, a little bit.
I'm surprised your boat
didn't sink a long time ago.
What? It's a better boat
than that rust bucket of yours.
[barking and grunting]
Granddad Dog and Grandpa Pig
are very best friends.
Catch this, captain.
Aye, aye, skipper.
[engine starts]
Granddad Dog's truck has lifted
Grandpa Pig's boat out of the water.
[Peppa and George] Wow.
Next stop, the boatyard.
[Peppa] What's a boatyard?
A boatyard, Peppa,
is where broken boats get mended.
This is Grampy Rabbit's boatyard.
Ahoy there, me hearties.
Ahoy there, Grampy Rabbit.
Whoo. Who did that to your boat,
Grandpa Pig?
Um, someone drove it into a mooring post.
It went crash.
And made a big hole there.
You should never let other people
steer your boat, Grandpa Pig.
Uh... Yes. Can you mend it?
Of course.
I just need to size up the damage.
Grampy Rabbit is measuring the hole
in Grandpa Pig's boat.
Now I need to find something
to patch it up.
[grunts] It must be good
to know how to mend a boat.
Oh. It takes years
to learn how to mend a boat.
How long have you been mending boats?
Years.
Grampy Rabbit has collected
lots of scrap metal to mend boats with.
Now, this is a gold mine.
It's a pile of rubbish.
Ah, but you can make things
from piles of rubbish.
Like what?
[Grampy Rabbit] Like submarines.
[Peppa and George] Wow.
Grampy Rabbit has made
a submarine out of rubbish.
Does it actually work?
Watch this.
It fills up with water.
So, it's very good at going down.
But not so good at coming back up.
Now, this is what I've been looking for.
It's a washing machine.
It's the fix for Grandpa Pig's boat,
is what it is.
You're going to mend my boat
with a bit of washing machine?
Yes.
That's as good as new.
Hooray!
Now we test it.
Prepare for launch.
Aye, aye.
Amazing. It floats.
-You sound surprised.
-Yes, usually they sink on the first go.
[grunts] Now we can go for our day
on the river.
What a splendid idea.
This is the life.
Out on a boat,
with just the sea and the sky.
I know a song about the sea and the sky.
Do you want to hear it?
No, thank you.
Yes, please.
♪ I got up this morning ♪
♪ The sea was still there ♪
♪ And so was the sky ♪
[all laugh]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her friends
are at playgroup.
Today, children,
we are going to learn about instruments
that you shake, rattle, and bang.
Hooray!
First choose an instrument each
from the music room.
[chattering and giggling]
I've got drums.
They are called bongo drums, Danny.
You bang them with your hands like this:
[bleats] I've got a flat bongo drum.
That is a bodhran. It Is Irish.
You beat it with a little stick,
like this:
I've got a tambourine.
Very good, Pedro.
You can also shake it like this:
[all] Ooh.
[grunts] I've got a big drum.
Ah! The bass drum.
[meows] I don't know what this is called,
but it's scrape-y.
That, Candy, is called a guiro,
and it comes all the way
from South America.
[in unison] Wow.
How did it get here?
I brought it back from my holiday.
What are these?
They are maracas.
I brought them back
from my holiday in Spain.
-This is a triangle.
-[dings]
My dad sells these in boxes of ten.
Thank you, Freddy, I will remember that.
You don't need to go on holiday
to get them.
Thank you.
[trumpets]
What are these?
These are castanets.
-My dad sells them in boxes of five.
-Thank you, Freddy.
[clicking]
Olé!
That is how you play the castanets.
Here you are, Emily.
Do I have to do the dance?
[laughs] No. Just make
the clickety-clack noise.
-[clicking]
-[giggles]
Ah. I see Rebecca has cymbals.
[squeaks] Yes.
[laughs]
Now you know
what your instruments sound like,
we can play them all together.
-Ready...
-Steady, go.
Stop, stop, stop.
That is not music. That is just noise.
Anybody can bang, bang, bang.
But to make music,
you have to listen to each other,
and keep in time.
Madame Gazelle,
I can't listen and do music.
Can you clap?
Yes.
If you can clap, you can make music.
All the girls, please, copy me.
Now boys.
Madame Gazelle
has made the clapping into music.
And stop.
[all giggle]
Now we will learn how
to play our instruments together.
The parents have come
to pick up the children.
Ah, you're just in time.
May I present
The Shake, Rattle and Bang Orchestra.
Hooray!
Children, ready, steady, go.
Bravo.
Perhaps some of my old pupils
would like to join in, too.
Find your instruments, children.
[in unison] Yes, Madame Gazelle.
Madame Gazelle used to teach
all the mommies and daddies
when they were little.
It's quite hard, Daddy,
but you do it like this:
Let me see if I've got that right.
Daddy, you can play the drums.
I am a bit of an expert at drumming.
That's good shake, rattle, and banging.
Now for a tune.
My daddy can shake, rattle, and bang.
[laughing]